ELLIE HEALY

elliehealy20@outlook.com 🕻 07565815206 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/ellie-healy/

Portfolio: https://e-healy.github.io/ehealy-portfolio/

Ambitious marketing creative and Modern Languages graduate from the University of Warwick, with a strong analytical background and passion for technology and data; I enjoy building digital experiences that are accessible and enjoyable. Self-motivated with a can-do attitude, I possess excellent communication skills which I desire to combine with my technical skills and creativity to craft meaningful digital applications. In any role, I strive to be a solution-focused and proactive collaborator that always drives success.

KEY SKILLS

Technical Skills: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Java, React, Git, IOS Development, Agile, SwiftUI, SQL, Jira, Confluence, VSCode.

Languages: English, Spanish, French, Italian, Chinese.

EDUCATION

University of Warwick

BA Hispanic Studies with Italian (Honours), including a year of mandarin, 2:1

Sept 2019 - July 2023

Universidad Pablo de Olavide

Jan - May 2022

ERASMUS University Placement. Subjects: Introduction to Finance, Business Management and Translation

New Hall School 2012-2019

A Levels: English Literature, Spanish and French ABB

GCSES: 10 GCSES graded A*-B: English Literature: (8), English Language (7), Mathematics (7), French (A*),

Spanish (A*), History (A*), Theology (A*), Biology (B), Chemistry (B), Physics (B)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Marketing and Web Developer Volunteer We Make Change, ETC Vibes - Remote

Feb 2024 - Present

- Collaborating with design team to translate visual concepts into a responsive, user-friendly website.
- Executing digital marketing campaigns to enhance learning experiences for 1500+ students who lack access to quality educational resources

Digital Content Assistant (6 month fixed contract) Speedy Automotive Security - Remote

Sept 2023 - Feb 2024

- · Collaborated with the team to create a successful content plan through analysis of algorithm success and maintaining good client relations, enhancing business sales by 15%.
- Amplified the company's online professional profile and brand recognition by keeping up to date with the latest digital media trends.
- Exceeded analytics targets through the growth of TikTok following to 50,000 followers with over 10,000,000 views.

Administration and Marketing Assistant Premier Recruit Ltd - London

June - August 2022

- 3-month work placement between university in which I enhanced the company's recruitment strategy by exploring diverse channels of advertising via digital platforms.
- Leveraged graphic design tools such as Canva and Adobe Photoshop to create eye-catching job posts, which generated a 33% increase in job applicants.
- Utilised Microsoft Excel to organise job applicant data and converted data into pivot tables.

Finance and IT work experience

July - August 2017

Credit Suisse - London

- Intensive summer work experience where I participated in activities within professionals departments such as IT, finance, and cybersecurity.
- Worked successfully within a team environment when completing diverse cybersecurity projects.
- Created an advertisement for the company with the aim of promoting its values to potential clients and future employers.

Catering and Events Volunteer New Hall Voluntary Service - Chelmsford

- Planned and served a three-course meal to the elderly weekly, I catered to guests by engaging in fulfilling conversations about themselves through a diplomatic approach.
- Organised the planning of a summer day camp project for 50+ disadvantaged and disabled children

CERTIFICATIONS

In my free time, I enjoy upskilling so that I am continuously pushing the limits of what I am capable of. Check out some of my upskilling projects below:

Software Engineering Virtual Work Experience (ongoing) - Skyscanner
 Developing key technical skills across diverse software engineering roles.

2024

- Introduction to JavaScript (sponsored by Activision Blizzard) Code First Girls
 Achievements: Winner for outstanding efforts in final project. 8-week intensive JavaScript course
- Introduction to Web Development (sponsored by QinetiQ) Code First Girls
 Achievements: Winner for outstanding efforts in final project. 8-week intensive Web Dev course
- Code First Girls MOOC Sprints: Introduction to Agile & Scrum Methodologies, Introduction to Java, Introduction to IOS Development, Introduction to Python & Coding
- · Getting Started with Python Bright Network

2023

• Fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google